二零二一年陕西省初中学业水平考试英语听力部分。二零。二一年陕西省初中学业水平考试英语听力部分。
Exclusive Exclusive
第一大题听对话选答案。第一节，听下。面十段对话，每段对话后有一个问题，读两遍。请根据每段对话的内容和后面的问题，从所给的三个选项中选出最恰当的一项。
Exclusive Exclusive Exclusive
Exclusive Exclusive
Exclusive Exclusive Exclusive Exclusive
Series Exclusive Exclusive
Exclusive Exclusive
第二节，听下面两段对话，每段对话后有几道小题，请根据每段对话的内容，从所给的问题和三个选项中选出最恰当的一项。每段对话读两遍。听第十一段对话，回答第十一、十二小题。张。
Hi, John. What do you like doing in your free time?
I like drawing pictures and collecting erasers.
And you? I like collecting coins.
How many erasers have you collected?
About 50. Wow!
So many! Yeah, some of them are my birthday gifts, others are my prizes.
听第十二段对话，回答第十三至十五小。
Father's Day is coming.
I'm going to give a surprise to my dad.
Sounds great. What's your plan, Mary?
Last year, I made a card for my father to show my love.
This year, I'm going to cook a meal for him.
Really? What would you like to cook?
Beef noodles. They are his favorite.
I think I should do something special for my father too.
I haven't seen him for a few weeks.
Then why not write a letter to him,
Good idea. Father's Day is coming.
I'm going to give a surprise to my
Sounds great. What's your plan, Mary?
Last year, I made a card for my father to show my love.
This year, I'm going to cook a meal for him.
Really? What would you like to cook?
Beef noodles. They are his favorite.
I think I should do something special for my father too.
I haven't seen him for a few weeks.
Then why not write a letter to him,
Good idea. Hi, Jimmy.
第二大题：听独白，填信息。本题你将听到一段独白，读两遍，请根据。去读白内容，用所听到的单词或短语完成下列各题，每空限填一个单词。
This is Yaping.
Thank you for your last call.
I'm so glad to hear that you are coming to China to learn Kung Fu in a school in my
hometown. I'm sure you'll have a good time.
In fact, I started to learn Kung Fu when I was seven years old.
But I didn't practice much because I was too busy with my schoolwork.
I really like Kung Luckily, I'll go home in two weeks for the coming summer
vacation. Then I can find some time to learn it again.
I'm so happy we can practice together every day.
Please call or email me when you hear this message and let me know when you will
arrive. Best wishes to you for coming to China to learn and practice Kung Fu.
I'll go to the airport by car and meet you there.
I really hope to see you soon.
Hi, Jimmy. This is Yaping.
Thank you for your last call.
I'm so glad to hear that you are coming to China to learn Kung Fu in a school in my
hometown. I'm sure you'll have a good time.
In fact, I started to learn Kung Fu when I was seven years old.
But I didn't practice much because I was too busy with my schoolwork.
I really like Kung Fu.
Luckily, I'll go home in two weeks for the coming summer vacation.
Then I can find some time to learn it again.
I'm so happy we can practice together every day.
Please call or email me when you hear this message and let me know when you will
arrive. Best wishes to you for coming to China to learn and practice Kung Fu.
I'll go to the airport by car and meet you there.
I really hope to see you soon.